I've always wanted to be a "Smash Bros: Melee" pro ever since I saw their earnings last week.
I want to go to the world cup win the final, take on the soviets and become the smash champion!
But there was a huge problem: I have never played this game before.
Fortunately there's an over-representation of Swedish winners, so I'm guessing it's genetic.
First I need to pick a main-
I know fox is the best character and the most commonly played..
Meaning people know how to beat him, making him the worst character.
I'm gonna main Mewtwo, because he's level 70 and could blow up a building.
But there was a huge problem-
No idea how to unlock him.
I need to play for 20 hours!
But if I play a guy for 20 hours that WILL become my main-
So I need my main to unlock my main. That's a CatcH-22
-No.. it's a "gotta catch them all 22"!
I guess I have to pick a new main..
I can't pick Falco because apparently that ain't him and I don't trust this guy or this girl
that leaves me with:
The guy I should have picked from the start.
Yes I know he's basically just catch-phrase and win.
But I still gotta play thousands of matches in training mode, because the grind never stops!
[TRAINING MONTAGE MUSIC]
I Have played-
Five Matches.
I think I'm ready! but first I should check out my competition
I'll never be this good even if I play a million matches because my problem is game understanding.
Characters gets hit and therefore are easier to knock out. How does that even work?
I need to know the science of smashing- not what I was looking for.
The problem isn't that people knock me out.
It's that I don't know how to triple jump and since no one wants to teach me how to-
I Guess I'll have to switch main again to a guy that can't get knocked out
Yeah, I'm gonna main a master hand.
YES
I AM INVINCIBLE
Now I'll destroy the world championship!
But there was a huge problem-
There is no world championship...
All this work.. for nothing...
Wait, no this is a good thing!
This means I can create IT!
so I contacted Nintendo about hosting a smash tournament-
I didn't say it was the world championship,
But I insinuated it and they responded: "bla bla Bla broadcasting rights bla bla".
They said no, and you see that's why I contacted Nintendo of America. I'm not American!
They have no power here!
Emailed Nintendo UK they responded: "fuck off mate".
Emailed Nintendo Japan, no idea what they responded but there was a huge no at the bottom.
I kept emailing Nintendo's until finally, Nintendo Argentina said: "No señor we los not belivo in you̇"
I don't know what that means-
So I'll take it!
I could now host the official "Smash Melee Championship"-
Without telling anyone.
Was gonna broadcast it on Twitch, in offline mode.
My opponent is a CPU "Pichu" main, the worst character,
So obviously that's what I'm facing.
(level 2 so it actually fights back so I can say that I beat it)
I was nervous.. but excited!
I could hear the audience shouting my name-
Even though I was very very alone..
I only have to beat this and I am officially the best smash player on the planet!
What followed was the grandest beating in E-sport history.
A "Pichu" bot is officially the best player in the world?
-And I need to see a psychiatrist!
[ENDING JINGLE]